import IQuestion, { QuestionType } from "../entity/Question";

const QuestionDataPart5 : IQuestion[] = [{
    id: 'p5_1101',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: ' Dr. Braun will write ------ letters only for interns who master every task expected of a junior copy editor.',
    answer: ['recommends ', 'recommendation', 'recommended', 'recommending'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1102',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The ------ of a new chief financial officer at Veracore Industries was announced on April 6.',
    answer: ['appoint', 'appoints', 'appointed', 'appointment'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1103',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'After a six-month probationary period, city employees are ------ to take vacation days.',
    answer: ['beneficial', 'eligible', 'convenient', 'relevant'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1104',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Ms. Larensky is applying with several different agencies to obtain the permits ------ for the outdoor art event.',
    answer: ['required', 'requiring', 'requires', 'will require'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1105',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'This letter serves as ------ that we have received and processed your credit-card cancellation request. Ms. Larensky is applying with several different agencies to obtain the permits 	for the outdoor art event.',
    answer: ['confirm', 'confirmed', 'confirmable', 'confirmation'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1106',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Many people at the company have industry experience, but only a handful of ------ can see the future importance of current trends',
    answer: ['we', 'us', 'our', 'ourselves'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1107',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The new furniture for the conference room is scheduled to be delivered ------ on Tuesday.',
    answer: ['hardly', 'comfortably', 'early', 'eagerly'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1108',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'After working in Canada for ten years, Cha Joon has ------ to Seoul to plan the opening of an upscale restaurant.',
    answer: ['visited', 'returned', 'occurred', 'related'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1109',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Toucan Database System is designed to perform a detailed financial analysis ------.',
    answer: ['automate', 'automatic', 'automated', 'automatically'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1110',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The city council approved the bill to increase funding for its road improvement ------',
    answer: ['statement', 'permission', 'project', 'ability'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1111',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The Neighborhood Involvement Program honors residents ------ volunteer their time to help Egin City.',
    answer: ['for', 'who', 'those', 'as'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1112',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Several architects ------ intriguing design plans for the Hadler Building’s addition.',
    answer: ['proposing', 'proposed', 'proposal', 'proposals'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
},  {
    id: 'p5_1113',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The updated training program is limited to site supervisors ------ the Casey Medical Care system.',
    answer: ['within', 'until', 'during', 'since'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
},{
    id: 'p5_1114',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Mr. Koizumi must complete the cost estimate before he ------ for the conference.',
    answer: ['will leave', 'leaves', 'leaving', 'left'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1115',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Although the new X150 printer is	------ to other models, it costs only half as much.',
    answer: ['similar', 'likable', 'reflected', 'considerate'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1116',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'To address budget deficits, Lunere County plans to limit spending and ------ tourism.',
    answer: ['promote', 'declare', 'obtain', 'benefit'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1117',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Operating instructions are posted above the printer so you can ------ refer to them.',
    answer: ['consecutivefy', 'standardly', 'namely', 'easily'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1118',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The Vickwell Historical Museum will be closed for renovations ------ on Monday, September 10.',
    answer: ['will begin', 'has begun', 'beginner', 'beginning'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1119',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Finley Plant Nursery implements the ------ latest agricultural techniques.',
    answer: ['so', 'much', 'very', 'much'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1120',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'According to the compensation guidelines, employees who regularly complete their work ------ it is due may receive bonuses.',
    answer: ['before', 'how', 'why', 'either'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1121',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Thank you for your ------ in the Foxdale Apartments community enhancement survey.',
    answer: ['participant', 'participation', 'participate', 'participated'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1122',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Solar energy has become a key ------ in the development of additional energy resources throughout the region.',
    answer: ['factor', 'position', 'instructor', 'composition'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1123',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'The LPN auto company has issued a special report to address concerns	------ the fuel efficiency of its vehicles.',
    answer: ['excluding', 'during', 'following', 'regarding'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1124',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'This year\'s company retreat will focus on techniques that help people think more ------ ',
    answer: ['create', 'creative', 'creativity', 'creatively'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1125',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Employees must ------ requests for time off to Ms. Cheung for approval.',
    answer: ['apply', 'submit', 'vacate', 'oppose'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1126',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Board members are free to discuss the issues among ------ before the formal votes are taken.',
    answer: ['themselves', 'theirs', 'their', 'they'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1127',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'Judging by ticket sales, Fen Jiang’s first attempt at directing a film was ------ a success.',
    answer: ['clear', 'clearly', 'clearer', 'clearing'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1128',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: '------ the Nolan Credit Union parking areais now open to the public, a section has been reserved for credit union employees.',
    answer: ['While', 'When', 'For', 'But'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1129',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: '	Pharmacy technicians are responsible for verifying and processing prescriptions	------ they are requested by a physician.',
    answer: ['as well as', 'as soon as', 'in regard to', 'in addition to'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    difficultLevel: 3
}, {
    id: 'p5_1130',
    type: QuestionType.part5,
    question: 'All laboratory personnel must attend the clinical safety workshop to ensure	 ------ with new regulations.',
    answer: ['activation', 'fulfillment', 'compliance', 'indication'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    difficultLevel: 3
}];

export default QuestionDataPart5;
